The toad lives in his fort underground.
癞蛤蟆住在他的地下城堡里
I know where to find him.
我知道去哪儿能找到他
Let's dig the toad out!
我们去把他挖出来
That is not going to work, mister.
这样行不通   先生
The fort is very deep.
他的城堡很深
And it's as complicated as a maze.
还和迷宫一样复杂
Emma, what do you think we should do?
Emma   你觉得我们该怎么办
I think, if we can become small enough, then we can get into the fort to find the crown.
我觉得   如果我们可以变得足够小   就能进到城堡里找王冠了
Get small? How?
怎么变小呢
Maybe Albert could help us.
或许Albert可以帮我们
Okay! Let's talk to Albert!
好   我们去找Albert
Albert! Albert!
He's not home.
他不在家
Where could he be?
他会去那儿了呢
Nathan do you know...
Nathan你知道
I don't think so.
我不觉得
Maybe he's at the beach.
也许他去沙滩了